malibunetwork.com 2012-05-25

# Privacy Policy

Last updated: June, 2010 This document contains information regarding the privacy policy and practice (hereinafter, "Privacy Policy) of Malibunetwork.com, a Mecheri Software & Social Web Applications company (hereinafter, "Malibunetwork.com") and is brought to you so you feel comfortable using our website, software and/or services. Malibunetwork.com is committed to investing great efforts in protecting the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy, which applies to all website, software and services provided under the Malibunetwork.com names and marks, explains how Malibunetwork.com treats personal information that we receive and collect. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION When you register to Malibunetwork.com website, service or software, Malibunetwork.com collects certain information such as your first and last name, e-mail address, location, age of birth, and as well as information about your use of Malibunetwork.com features and broadcasting of content (collectively, "User Information"). Additionally, when you use Malibunetwork.com website, software and/or services, Malibunetwork.com may access non-personal identifiable information, including, without limitation, the manner, consistency, duration and other information identifying the ways in which you and other users as whole use and access the Malibunetwork.com website, software and/or services (including any advertising thereon), and may aggregate various statistical and other data related to such use, including, without limitation, ascertaining aggregated usage patterns and other behavioral information. This information is collected as non-individually identifiable personal information. Any personal information voluntarily disclosed by you through e-mail, in public-view personal profiles, public-view uploaded materials, chat rooms, message boards, or intra-site message systems, can be seen and possibly used by others. Displaying personal information in such public way via our website, software or services may have unintended privacy implications for you. USE OF INFORMATION Your User Information may be used by us for providing the services as described in Bambuser Terms of Use; and communications related to the Malibunetwork.com services such as sending notices about new features, or other information of interest to you relating to the Malibunetwork.com services, website or software. If you are participating in our beta program, then, during the beta trial period, your membership in the beta program will result in your receiving emails and other forms of communications. After the beta period, you will be able to opt out of receiving these communications through this website. Malibunetwork.com will not distribute, sell or rent any of your User Information to other people or nonaffiliated companies (other than a business that acquires Malibunetwork.com or its assets and that will undertake to materially comply with this Privacy Policy) except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, you acknowledge, consent, and agree that Malibunetwork.com may access, preserve, use, and disclose your User Information, including content uploaded to or accessed from Bambuser's website, software and/or services, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) enforce the Malibunetwork.com Terms of Service and/or end user license agreement(s) with respect to our software; (b) respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third parties; (c) respond to your customer service requests; (d) comply with legal process; and/or (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Bambuser, its users, or the public. The Malibunetwork.com website, software and services are constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. User Information helps guide such changes and evolution. Accordingly, we may access non-personally identifiable information such as your computer's IP Address, and may gather aggregated information about your and other users' use of our website, software and/or services, including, without limitation, the manner, consistency, duration and other information identifying the ways in which you and other users as whole use and access the Bambuser website, software and/or services (including any advertising thereon). We also may aggregate various statistical and other data related to such use, including, without limitation, ascertaining aggregated usage, patterns and other behavioral information in order to expand and better develop our services to enhance your experience. This information does not include individually identifiable personal information. Our third party content providers, advertisers and affiliates may be provided some of this information or data regarding usage patterns, advertising display or interests, so that they too can better serve your needs and preferences, but such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION If you choose a User ID and password when you register with our website, software and/or services, your password will be known only to you unless you disclose it to others. At Malibunetwork.com, we take commercially reasonable organizational and technical steps to protect the privacy of your personal information stored in the Malibunetwork.com computer systems. Bambuser will make best efforts to ensure that your information will be accessible only by authorized employees of Malibunetwork.com who need to have access to this information in order to provide you with Malibunetwork.com service and all the activities related to such service. However, you should be aware that there is no data that is transmitted over the Internet that can be guaranteed 100% secure in transmission or safe from theft or illegal capture. NO SPYWARE We naturally acknowledge the negative impact spyware has had on the internet, as after being infected with spyware, people are less likely to download and try new software. We proudly say that to the best of our knowledge, the Bambuser software is free of spyware. COOKIES Malibunetwork.com places cookies on your computer to retain your individual preferences and improve your user experience with our website, software and services, as well as to tell us what features of our website, services or software are most popular. We do not store any personal identification information in cookies, nor do we use cookies to obtain any personal information from you. You can change the configuration of your browser in such a manner that you will not be able to receive any cookies during your use of the Bambuser services, software or website. In that event, your access or use of certain parts of our website, software or services, may be restricted. UPDATE/DELETE USER INFORMATION All of your User Information is located in your Personal Malibunetwork.com Profile. Your profile can be edited and deleted at any time, by logging in to Malibunetwork.com with your User ID and password, then entering the “Dashboard” page. You should make sure that you protect your password from disclosure because anyone that gains access to your password will be able to edit your profile. NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN Malibunetwork.com website, software and services are designed and maintained for an audience at 14 years old and above. For this reason every user registration asks for date of birth and our best efforts are made to ensure the integrity of our minimum age policy. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect personal information from any person under 14 years of age. THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS AND THIRD PARTY WEBSITES Malibunetwork.com allows third-parties including users of the Malibunetwork.com service, to serve advertisements within the Malibunetwork.com website or services. These third-parties may send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Malibunetwork.com websites and/or service. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. Additionally, Bambuser allows third parties including users of the Malibunetwork.com service to use the service through their website as a broadcaster or as a viewer. Malibunetwork.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third parties without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out through the website, services or software. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Malibunetwork.com to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser may conclude that you fit the description of the targeted audience. Such third parties may also use information regarding your use of the Malibunetwork.com website, service and/or software (such as the number of times you viewed an ad to determine which ads to deliver to you) but are restricted from using any personally identifiable information). You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third parties for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such third parties - advertisers or websites. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY Malibunetwork.com may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our website. In addition, the date at the top of this Privacy Policy will indicate when this policy has most recently been revised; we encourage you to periodically revisit this Privacy Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. Your continued use of the Malibunetwork.com website, software and/or services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. ACQUISITION OF COMPANY As Malibunetwork.com continues to develop its business, Malibunetwork.com might sell or purchase subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions as well as in the event Malibunetwork.com or substantially all of its assets or certain business units are acquired by a third party, personal information of Malibunetwork.com users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party. CONTACTING MALIBUNETWORK.COM If you have a privacy concern regarding any of Malibunetwork.com website, services, software, or this Privacy Policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the website, you should complete a feedback form or write to us by email at : privacy@malibunetwork.com.com. Alternatively, we can be reached at our postal mail address: Malibunetwork.com Mecheri Software & Social Web Applications Corp, Pacific Coast High Way Malibu, California 90265 Unites States of America
